Guide to the UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s UE.8.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- UE Films, October 1947 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- An Open Letter to the President of International Harvester, November 1947 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Profits Up, Prices Up, November 1947 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Let's Come Out Fighting Regarding Political Action, November 1947 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- People in Action Regarding Radio, November 1947 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Greetings Regarding Membership Kit, November 1947 (Box 2, Folder 155)
- In This Tomorrow Regarding Anti-communism, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 156)
- In This Tomorrow Regarding Anti-communism, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 157)
- The Sellout 80th Congress Regarding Political Action, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 158)
- A Vital Message to Farmers, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 159)
- What's Ahead Economics amd Congress of Industrial Organization, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Remember Regarding Political Action, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Report to Membership Meeting Regarding Local 203 and General Electric Negotiations, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 160)
- What's Cooking, Joe? Regarding Political Action, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Why High Food Prices? Regarding Prices and Wages, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 160)
- We Fought for Our Union Regarding Univis Leus Strikes, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Up Up Up...Why? Regarding Prices, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- 25 Million? Regarding Political Action, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- You Are in Danger Regarding Taft-Hartley, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- What is the Mohawk Valley Formula Regarding RemRand Strikes, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- UE Leads the Way Regarding Organization, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- It Pays to Belong to UE Regarding Membership Drive, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Fighting Back with PAC, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Why Wages Must Be Raised, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- The Case of Harold Christoffel Regarding United Auto Workers, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- A Short Course in Parliamentary Procedure, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Progressive Unity Caucus Regarding United Auto Workers Factionalism, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 163)
- We Can Have Peace Regarding Political Action, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 164)
- A Message to Farmers Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America Local 105, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Aims Regarding American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Let's Come Out Fighting Regarding Political Action, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 165)
- This Is Aimed at You Regarding Taft-Hartley and International Association of Machinists, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 166)
- The Case of Carl Marzani Regarding Marzani Jailing, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 167)
- The Case of Harold Christoffel, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Industry's Law Against the People Regarding Taft-Hartley, January 1948 (Box 3, Folder 168)
- The Militarizatoin of America, January 1948 (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Workers Need a Wage Increase, March 1948 (Box 3, Folder 169)
- What a Good Boy Am I Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, April 1948 (Box 3, Folder 170)
- What a Good Am I Regarding General Electric Negotiations, April 1948 (Box 3, Folder 170)
- A Law To Gag and Control the American People Regarding Mundtbell, May 1948 (Box 3, Folder 170)
- The UE Shop Steward, June 1948 (Box 3, Folder 171)
- New Party Founding Convention Regarding Progressive Party, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 172)
- Greetings Regarding Stewards Kit, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 172)
- UE Steward's Kit, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 173)
- You and Your Steward, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 173)
- Your UE News, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 173)
- What Do You Read? Regarding Publication List, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 174)
- Telling the Town! Regarding Publicity, July 1948 (Box 3, Folder 175)
- Is It True What They Say About Cohen? Regarding Anti-semistism, August 1948 (Box 3, Folder 176)
- Let's Go to Press Regarding Local Papers, August 1948 (Box 3, Folder 177)
- Your Rights Are In Danger Regarding Political Action and Civil Liberties, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- Foreign Aid to Help Build Peace Regarding Foreign Policy, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- Know Your Enemies Regarding Red-baiting and Factionalism, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- Repeal Taft-Hartley, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- CIO Needs Unity--Not Raiding!, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- Make Congress Act for the People, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 178)
- For Independent Political Action, September 1948 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- What Is The Real Threat to Our Security? Regarding General Electric and GE and Atomic Energy Commission, October 1948 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- What Is the Evansville Formula? Regarding Red-baiting, November 1948 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- The People Voted for Action, November 1948 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- Repeal Taft-Hartley, November 1948 (Box 3, Folder 179)
- Segregation in Washington, November 1948 (Box 3, Folder 180)
- What.. Regarding General Electric, December 1948 (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Wall of Sepatation Between Church and State Regarding Education, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 181)
- A Message to Teachers from a Labor Union, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Meet Henry Wallace Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 182)
- No Friend of Labor Regarding Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 182)
- Your Aching Heart Regarding Health, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 183)
- Keep Cool! Regarding Health, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 183)
- UE Publications, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 183)
- Who Done It Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- Increase Wages Out of Profits Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- The Case of the Fighting Fivespots Regarding Political Action and United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- Jim Crow Must Go, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- The People Can Win...in 48 Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- Call a Cop Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 185)
- Cancer Kills Regarding Health, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 186)
- What Do You Want Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 186)
- You Who Have Gathered Here Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- UE Guide to Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- He Thinks Right Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- I Have Seen Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- What Does 1948 Add Up To Regarding Political Action (Box 3, Folder 187)
- Before and After Regarding Taft-Hartley and Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- He's In Favor of the Draft 100% Regarding Political Action and Conscription, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- If You Work for a Living Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- Workers Aren't Fooled Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- We Ask Justice Regarding Fur and Leather Workers, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- UE Rebukes Lilienthal Regarding General Electric, Red-baiting and Atomic Energy Commission, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Help Wanted Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Tanks or Tractors Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- We Have a Choice Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Knock on Any Door Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Peace Freedom and Abundance Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- What About the Progressive Party Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- Not a Red Cent Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- Pork up, Hogs Down, Why Regarding United Packinghouse Workers, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- It Pays to Belong to UE Regarding District 5 and Organization, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 191)
- Fishy Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 191)
- The Case for the Insurance Man, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 191)
- It's Your Union They're After Regarding Red-baiting, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 192)
- Steps to Peace Regarding Political Action and Foreign Policy, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 193)
- Journey to Israel Regarding Foreign Policy and Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 193)
- Taking an Offensive Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 193)
- Corn Tells All Regarding Farmers and Prices, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 193)
- Frankly, Sir, I Need More Money Regarding Labor Cartoons, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 194)
- Facts to Fight With Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 195)
- So You're Wearing a Wallace Button Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 196)
- Let Us Add Years to Our Lives Regarding Political Action, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 196)
- Handbook for Organizers, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 197)
- Don't Buy Regarding Boycotts, and Hoover and Belmont Strikes, January 10, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 198)
- Boycott Kit Regarding Hoover and Belmont Strikes, January 1949 (Box 3, Folder 198)
- Don't Buy Pamphlet Edition Regarding Boycott, and Hoover and Belmont Strikes, January 1949 (Box 3, Folder 198)
- About UE Regarding Publicity, February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 198)
- Then And Now Regarding CWA, February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 198)
- New Evidence fo the Militarization of America, February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 199)
- New Evidence fo the Militarization of America, February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 200)
- A Message to Philco Workers Regarding Local 103, Local 101 and Factionalism, February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- $1000 Secret Local 101, Local 103 and Factionalism, February 1949 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- Putting the Record Straight Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, United Auto Workers, and Inter-union Rivalry, March 1, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- Cultural and Scientific Conference for World Peace, March 25, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- Build the Farmer-Labor Coalition Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, March 25, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- A Fair Labor Law Regarding General Electric and Political Action, March 1949 (Box 3, Folder 202)
- The Rank and File Said No Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America Inter-union Rivalry, April 1949 (Box 3, Folder 202)
- On May Day Regarding May Day Parade, April 1949 (Box 3, Folder 203)
- Settling That Grievance, May 1949 (Box 3, Folder 203)
- The CIO Must Fight for the People Regarding Factionalism and Inter-union Rivalry, May 1949 (Box 3, Folder 204)
- Keep America at Work Regarding Full Employment, June 1949 (Box 3, Folder 204)
- Trade Union International of Metal and Engineering Industries, June 1949 (Box 3, Folder 205)
- Unemployed, June 1949 (Box 3, Folder 206)
- Cho Meur Regarding Unemployment, June 1949 (Box 3, Folder 206)
- Ben Riskin Open Letter to UE Members Regarding Sylvania Negotiations, July 6, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 206)
- Economic Power of Unions Regarding American Iron and Steel Institute, August 1949 (Box 3, Folder 207)
- \Watchdog and Yardstick Regarding Farm Coops, August 1949 (Box 3, Folder 207)
- What Do You Read Regarding Media, October 1949 (Box 3, Folder 208)
- 34 Million Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization and Factionalism, October 1949 (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Program, Organization Convention, IUE Regarding IUE, November 28, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Your UE News, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Greetings Regarding Membership Kit, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 208)
- You and Your Steward, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Your Right to Run Your Own Union Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Your Seniority and Job Security Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Your Incentive Rates and Nights Shift Bonus Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Your Paid Holidays, Vacations, and Overtime Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1949 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- Constitution of the Trade Unions of the USSR, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Resolution of the Tenth Congress of Trade Unions of the USSR, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 211)
- I Learned About Communism the Hard Way Regarding Red-baiting, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 211)
- The Book of Needs Regarding United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 212)
- FE Raid and File Replies to Murray and Reuther, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 213)
- UAW Signs Secret No Raid Pact with IAM, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 213)
- What Happened to the National Union Strikers Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 213)
- Report on Israel Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 214)
- The Truth Regarding Pensions and United Steeworkers of America Negotiations, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Referendum Proposition Regarding Mergers and FE-UE, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Drive Out the Company Stooges Regarding Factionalism, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 215)
- What's Wrong with This Picture Regarding Housing and Blacks, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 216)
- International Harvester Double Talk Regarding International Harvester Negotiations, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 216)
- The People Who Make Singer Products Ask Your Help Regarding Strikes and Boycott, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 216)
- How Long Will You Stay in the Black Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 216)
- 25 Words Can Do It Regarding Political Action and Taft-Hartley, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 216)
- Why We Fight Back Regarding FE-UAW Inter-Union Rivalry, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 217)
- UE Acts Against Raiding and Dictatorship in the CIO, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 217)
- UE Acts Against Raiding and Dictatorship in the CIO, Small Edition, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 217)
- CWA Regarding Coal Miners and Railroad Workers, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 217)
- Free Trade Unions Remain in the WFTU, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 218)
- The CIO Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- 100 McCormick Workers Speak Regarding UAW-FE Inter-union Rivalry, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- Robbed a Bank Regarding UAW-FE Inter-union Rivalry, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- Is the Depression Here Regarding Farmers and Political Action, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- FE Fights Regarding Negotiations, Wages and United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 220)
- A Budget for Abundance Regarding Progressive Party, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 220)
- UE vs. Company Unionism Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 221)
- Parliamentary Procedure, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 221)
- Loyalty Oath Regarding Red-baiting, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 222)
- Company Unionism Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 1950 (Box 3, Folder 223)
- The Proud Record of an American Union Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 1950 (Box 4, Folder 224)
- The UE Record Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 1950 (Box 4, Folder 225)
- FEPC Regarding Political Action and Fair Employment Practices Commission, February 1950 (Box 4, Folder 225)
- It's Your Fight Too, Textile Edition Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization Inter-union Rivalry, February 1950 (Box 4, Folder 225)
- It's Your Fight Too, Steel Edition Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 1950 (Box 4, Folder 225)
- Carey Joins the Union Wreckers Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 1950 (Box 4, Folder 225)
- The Proud Record of an American Union, Second Edition, February 1950 (Box 4, Folder 226)
- UE Fights for Negro Rights Regarding CIO Inter-union Rivalry, March 20, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 227)
- He Had Enough Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 1950 (Box 4, Folder 228)
- Red-Baiting, March 1950 (Box 4, Folder 228)
- UE Westinghouse Vets Speak Out for Their Country and Union Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 229)
- An Open Letter to GE Workers in All Service Shops Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 229)
- A Message from GE Workers in Conneaut to GE Workers in Providence Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 229)
- I Resign Regarding CIO Inter-union Rivalry, April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 229)
- They Cannot be Trusted Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 229)
- A Message from UE Local 601 Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 229)
- What Kind of Teachers for Your Child Regarding Red-baiting and Teachers, May 1950 (Box 4, Folder 230)
- UE Defends Democracy and Religious Freedom Regarding ACTU, Red-baiting and UE Inter-union Rivalry, May 1950 (Box 4, Folder 230)
- The Facts Speak for Themselves Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization Inter-union Rivalry, May 1950 (Box 4, Folder 231)
- Frame-up Regarding Red-baiting, June 1950 (Box 4, Folder 232)
- Stop the Frame-ups Against Our Union, August 1950 (Box 4, Folder 232)
- Blind Hysteria Regarding Red-baiting, October 1950 (Box 4, Folder 232)
- One Union Regarding Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America Founding Convention, October 1950 (Box 4, Folder 233)
- The High Price of Milk Regarding Co-ops, November 1950 (Box 4, Folder 233)
- Statement of Policy Regarding National Committee for Peaceful Alternatives, December 1950 (Box 4, Folder 233)
- Let's Join the Human Race Regarding Foreign Policy, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 234)
- Why a Labor Leader is Being Framed Regarding Weber Case, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 234)
- Checklist of UNESCO Publications, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 234)
- UE Shows the Way on Pensions or Insurance Regarding Local 610 and Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
- Why Politicians Red-Bait, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
- UE Airbrake Vets Nail Another IUE-CIO Lie Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
- UE Defends Democracy and Religious Freedom Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
- Where Is the CIO Going Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization and United Office and Professional Workers of America Records Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
- UE Has Really Delivered the Goods Regarding Women, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
- Time to Catch Up Regarding Westinghouse Negotiationsm Pensions and Insurance, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
- They Helped Build Your Union Regarding Red-baiting, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
- The Union for GE Lamp Workers Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
- A Message to Salaried Employees Regarding Organization and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
- An Important Message to All Westinghouse Women Workers Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
- It's a Trick Regarding Red-baiting and Mine-Mill, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
- ACTU, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 237)
- Big 3 United in UE Regarding General Electric and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 237)
- One Union, One Contract, GE Edition Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 238)
- One Union, One Contract, W Edition Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 238)
- UE Guide to Fair Practices Regarding Women and Blacks, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 238)
- Farmer's Union Regarding Farm Policy, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 239)
- Fellow Citizens: Our Husbands Are In Prisons Regarding Red-baiting, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 239)
- An American Mother Jailed and Hounded Regarding Sentner Case and Red-baiting, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 240)
- Your Union and Others Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 240)
- Bad Boss? There Ain't No Such--Says Riesel Regarding Red-baiting, January 1951 (Box 4, Folder 241)
- A Plot that Labor Must Smash Regarding Bridges Case and International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union, February 28, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 241)
- From the Testimony Regarding Red-baiting, Emspak-Quinn Case, March 1951 (Box 4, Folder 241)
- The Facts About High Living Costs, April 24, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 242)
- The Facts About High Living Costs, April 24, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 243)
- The People Have Too Little, Not Too Much Regarding Wage Stabilization Board, April 1951 (Box 4, Folder 244)
- The Facts About High Living Costs, June 1951 (Box 4, Folder 245)
- UE Freedom Festival, September 20, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 246)
- Why the Strike Vote Regarding General Electric Negotiations, October 1951 (Box 4, Folder 246)
- Why the Strike Vote Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, October 1951 (Box 4, Folder 246)
- The McCarran Act Regarding Political Action and Civil Liberties, October 1951 (Box 4, Folder 246)
- Questions and Answers on the UE Fighting Fund, October 1951 (Box 4, Folder 246)
- A Fighting Fund, November 1951 (Box 4, Folder 246)
- 75,000 Workers Went to UE Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, November 1951 (Box 4, Folder 247)
- Who Does The Work Regarding Childrens Book, November 1951 (Box 4, Folder 247)
- Our Economic Policy at Home and Abroad Regarding Committee for Economic Development, November 1951 (Box 4, Folder 248)
- Labor Unity to End the Wage Freeze, December 1951 (Box 4, Folder 248)
- 75,000 Workers Went to UE, Second Edition, December 1951 (Box 4, Folder 248)
- American Workers Look at the Soviet Union, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 249)
- The Great Construction Works of the Soviet Union, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 250)
- The Achievements of Soviet Economics in the First Postwar Five Year Plan, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 251)
- The Soviet Trade Unions, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 252)
- Mikhail Sinitsyn Urals Metalworker, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 253)
- Fighting Communism in Unions, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 254)
- Jim Crow Justice in Korea, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 254)
- Raise Rather Than Lower the People's Standard of Living Regarding Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 255)
- The Heat Is On Regarding Civil Rights Congress and Civil Liberties, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 255)
- What to Do If Arrested, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 255)
- UE Fights for the People Regarding Red-baiting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 255)
- Murdered Regarding Racism and Health-care, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- Purged Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Local 1227, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- This Is Our Union Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- Friend of Court Brief Request Regarding Blacks and Willie McGee Case, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- One Step Leads to Another Regarding Red-baiting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- Fights for Unionism and Peace Regarding Scherer Case and Red-baiting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 256)
- Why the Frame-ups Regarding Red-baiting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 257)
- $6,719 Regarding Emerson Negotiations and UE Inter-union Rivalry, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 258)
- Labor Will Break the Wage Freeze, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 258)
- Why the Frame-ups, Large Edition Regarding Red-baiting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 258)
- Stop the Attack on Our Living Standards, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 258)
- The UE Record Speaks for Itself Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 258)
- Justice in the Rosenberg Case, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 259)
- The Races of Mankind Regarding Racism, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 260)
- Fraud Exposed Regarding Inflation, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 260)
- The Contest Regarding Farmers and Political Action, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 261)
- Let's Talk About the Real Issue Regarding Foreign Policy, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 261)
- The Longer Workers Wait to Rejoin UE Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, January 1952 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- Together We Win Regarding Women, January 1952 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- Tax Day Regarding Taxation and Political Action, February 1952 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- The Shameful Record of IUE-CIO Leaders in the Otis Strike, February 1952 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- Go Back to Work Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, Strikes and Seeger, February 1952 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- Men's Business Too Regarding Women, February 1952 (Box 4, Folder 262)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, Sixth Edition, February 1952 (Box 4, Folder 263)
- Speed-up, February 1952 (Box 4, Folder 264)
- Pity the Poor Boss Regarding General Electric and Wages, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 264)
- Go Back to Work Regarding inter-union rivlary: IUE Inter-union Rivalry, Strikes and Seeger, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 264)
- The Longer Workers Wait to Rejoin the UE Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 264)
- Guess Regarding Profits, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 264)
- One Day Out of Four Regarding Taxation and Political Action, March 1952 (Box 4, Folder 264)